我回家了
I am home
亲爱的
Hi honey
今晚就我们两个 我们可以出去吃晚饭
we are on our own tonight,I thought maybe we go out to dineer
孩子们呢
Where are the kids?
Malcolm在Stevie家 Reese有冰球练习
Malcolm is over Stevie's Reese's got a hockey practice
Deewy在Billy家或者某个邻居小孩家
Dewey's at Billy's or one of the neighborhood kids
所以只有我们两个
So we are on our own
你今晚想干什么
What do you in the mood for?
简直是速度的新纪录了
That is gotta be a new record
大家总要我们做志愿者
people are always asking our class to volunteer for stuff
他们认为我们什么都不会做 被社会抛弃
They just assume we are social rejects with nothing better to do
这是真的
And it's true
我只是不喜欢被人当面指出来
I just don't like any thrown on my face
我们学校需要你们这样大的孩子参加我们的舞台剧
So our school needs a kid about your age to be in our school play
会很有趣的
We are a lot of fun!
是威廉莎士比亚的剧
The play is by a guy named William Shakespeare
他是很久以前的作家
He was a writer way back in olden times
他是个患有梅毒的酒鬼
He was a syphilitic drunk fronting
空有一个十四世牛津伯爵的头衔
for the 14th Earl of Oxford
为什么你老是这么说
Why can not you leave the part alone!
他确实没有高学历
So he didn't have the benefit of higher education
李尔王又有几个Phd
How many Phd is the great King Lear
淡定 我们有客人在这里
now now try to remember we have a guest
让我们把激烈讨论放在周五的公开论坛好么
Let's save our heated words for our open forum Friday
Megan 继续
Megan continue
无论他是谁
Whoever he was
他有一点小胡子
He had a pointed litter beard
还写了部很棒的剧叫"仲夏夜之梦"
and he wrote a really good play called "MidSummer Nights Dream"
换儿 仲夏夜之梦角色 演仙后的侍从
我们需要一个群众演员来演换儿
We need someone to play the changeling boy
在大家兴奋之前 我先说明不利的方面
Okay before anyone gets too excited there is a downside
- 就是可能会缺课  - 我愿意参加
- you'll probablely have to miss class - I will do it!
不行 我们正在研究一个秘密项目
He can't! We were working on a secret project that
我说太多了
I've said too much
我以为我们已经同意 不再有任何秘密项目
Okay, I thought we agree, no more secret projects
你们有些人上次烧掉的眉毛还没有长回来
Some of you still don't have your eyebrows back from your last secret project
- 我可以兼顾  - 好吧
- I can do both - All right
只要你弄清哪个优先就可以了
Just as long as you know your where your priorities are
我走了
I can go now
之前我觉得她很无聊
I used to think she was so
但是她双性倾向之后 她酷多了
boring but after she's bi-curious she's just so much I don't know cooler
太对了
Oh my God! That is so true!
双性之后她好像完全变了个人
She's like totally changed the personalities she's been wheat
哦你听说了么
Oh, and have you heard?
Mark终于不搞那档子摇摆乐了
Mark is totally out of that swing thing which is so over, and into goth...
我读过
oh!
是本好书
I read that That's really a good book
那是Travis 他有焦虑症
That's Travis. He has angst
看看这些人
Look at all these people!
他们打洞 沉思 穿奇怪的衣服
They are pierced.They are brooding.They are wearing wired clothes
他们不在乎任何事
They don't care about anything!
就好像满屋子的Francis
It's like a room full of Francises
大家注意了
Okay, people!
我们开始排第二场第三幕
We are doing the Act 3 scene 2
Oberon和Puck
Oberon, Puck
- 我的Puck在哪  - 他应该有摔跤比赛
- Where's My Puck? - I think he has a wrestling meet.
喂 你
Hey, you!
演换儿那小孩儿
Changeling boy
- 你识字吗  - 识字
- Can you read? - Yeah
我们要给没来的孩子一点教训
we gotta half these kids beat
Puck 角色之一 又名好人罗宾
念Puck的台词 27页
Read Puck for the day page 27
这是你的疏忽
This is thy negligence:
仍旧是你做错了
still thou mistakest
否则就是你在任意妄为
Or else committ'st thy knaveries wilfully
相信我 陛下 是我疏忽了
Believe me, king of shadows, I mistook
你不是告诉过我
Did not you tell me I should know
希腊人的品行吗
The man by the Athenian garment be had on?
目前为止清白证明了
And so far blameless proves my enterprise,
我没有辜负希腊人 有着一样的眼睛
That I have nointed an Athenian's eyes and so far
你在高中舞台剧里 从没有
You went from a part
台词的角色变成了主角
with no lines to the lead in a high school play?
不错 不是音乐剧吧
That's great! That's not musical is it?
- 不是  - 太好了
- No - That's great!
你演一个精灵
Dude you play a fairy!
不是随便的精灵 是剧里最大只的
Not just any fairy Reese! He's the biggest fairy in a whole play!
真为你骄傲
I'm so proud of you
排练是每天晚上 必须5点把我送到那里
rehearsals are every night. You have to get me there by 5
每天晚上
Every night?
是的 周末要做场景道具
oh, yeah we build sets on the weekends
好吧 除非Reese被留校
Okay we can do this
否则我就可以早点上班
if I go to work early I can get off in enough time to drop you off at rehearsals
在Reese打冰球之前
before I take Reese to hockey
送你去排练的地方
except the days Reese is detention
这样Dewey就一个人了
And then Dewey is home alone
我来 这几周重新调整下工作
I'll it take care of it, I can rearrange my schedule for a couple of weeks
我们一起一定很开心
It'll be fun spending some time together
可以像上次一样用车压东西吗
Can we run over things the car like we did last time?
它已经死了
It was already dead
Joe 这是目前最棒的酱汁
This is your best guacamole yet, Joe
谢谢
Thanks
秘诀在于新鲜的莱姆汁
The secret is fresh lime juice
长官到
Commander on the floor
不要让我打扰你们
no, please. Don't let me disturb you
你们随意 就像自己家一样
make yourselves at home
等一下
Wait a minute
这里不是你的家
This is not your home
这里不是你母亲的家
This is not your Mama's house
这里没有女佣清理你们的玩具
There is no maid here to clean up your toys
在这个学习的地方
And yet, I look around this institution of learning
我看到了电子游戏 裸露的杂志
I see video games. I see girlie magazines
Garth Brooks，美国乡村音乐歌手
还有Garth
and I see Garth
Garth Brooks，美国乡村音乐歌手
Darth Vader 星球大战的角色 长官搞混了
Garf Vader 正在玷污我们的纪念墙
Garf Vader, defiling our Wall of remebering
很明显这里有些混乱
Well clearly things have got a little lax around here
我怪我自己 但是接受惩罚的是你们
I blame myself, but it is you who will suffer
从现在开始 每周检查
From now on there will be weekly inspections
所有非标准的个人情感和艺术品
and you will relinquish all nonstandard-issue personal
都将被没收
affects and artwork
是时候明白真正的快乐来自服从的时候了
It's time for you to learn that true happiness comes from within
这就是为什么您如此快乐吗 长官
So why you are so happy sir?
我快乐的像学生妹一样
I'm as giddy as a Schoolgirl, Cadet
清洁剂 Malcolm戏服上的亮片
Okay， get each other cleaner, glitter for Malcolm's costume
就是这些了
I think that's it
天那 怎么可能
Oh my god! Is that right?
- 请问现在几点 - 5:45
- What time do you have? - 5:45
5:45
这不可能
That's not possible I
我送了Malcolm 接了Reese 晚饭也在烧
Dropped off Malcolm, picked up Reese. Dinner is in the oven
怎么了
What is it?
我有25分钟的空闲
I have the next 25 minutes free
你怎么安排的 是不是落了个孩子
How did you manage that? Did you leave a kid somewhere?
没有 都安排好了
no. They are all accounted for
- 你准备干什么  - 我不知道
- What do you gonna do? - I don't know
我不知道
I don't know
- 这个放这里  - 是的 没错
- So this goes here? - Yeah, that should do it
原来这里有英文
hey, these were in English
真漂亮 我一个人做的时候可没发现是个盒子
this is nice, never looks like the box when I do it alone
我也是
Me either
我们合作的真好
We make a good team
你从主要道路开始建 我从大学开始
All right, you start on the main street I'll do university place.
我们在酒吧汇合 中午左右怎么样
we'll meet in the bistro say noon-ish
- 您需要按摩吗  - 我不确定
- Would you like a massage? - I Don't know
- 我不是个享受的人  - 只要15分钟
- I'm really not a massage person - It only takes 15 minutes
好吧
Well
我确实有些时间
I do have some to time to kill
我不会脱上衣的
I am not taking off my shirt
而且我警告你 我从没被催眠或者放松过
and I am warning you, I never been hypnotized and I never been relaxed
事实上
actually feels
感觉
feels
不错
pretty good
哀求他的爱人的眷怜
Pleading for a lover's fee
我们要喜欢他们的盛宴么
Shall we their fond pageant see
上帝啊 他们是多么的愚蠢
Lord, what fools these mortals be
你让我伤心Malcolm了
I'm very upset with you Malcolm
你让我又一次有了感觉
You made me care again
- Maicolm 刚才太棒了  - 我愿意不惜一切变得像你一样
- Malcolm that was terrific! - God I give anything to be as good as you!
你现在就这么棒
And if you are this good now
15岁时一定令人难以置信
imagining how amazing you're gonna be when you are 15
15岁时一定也很可爱
and think how cute he's gonna be when he is 15
天那 我刚是痴笑吗
oh my god, did I just giggle?
你刚痴笑了吗
Did you just giggle
Stevie 你来干什么
"Stevie, what are you doing here?
你没有来开会
You missed the meeting
你正在破
You jeopardize
坏
ing
我们的项目
our project
好 课上见
Great, see you in class
我想我是否可以直接上高中
I wonder if I could just go straight  to high school?
我老听说跳级会有社交障碍
I've been told skipping grades stunts you socially
但是我觉得被骗了
but I think I've been lied to
但是长官 这是我妹妹的照片
But sir, that's a photo of my sister!
对你她是妹妹 对其他学员是分心的东西
To you she is your sister. to the others cadets, she is a distraction
如果你需要我进一步解释 我会很耐心的
Now, if you need me to go into more detail on that. I will
学员 你的鬓角多长
How long are those sideburns Cadet?
这太扯了
This is crazy!
即使囚犯都能有照片
Even prisoners can have photographs
Spangler想让我们忘记我们还是人类
Spangler trying to take away the things that remind us we're still human
Francis 不要找麻烦
Francis, don't rock the boat
和我无关了
I don't care anymore
是时候把最后的绝望转化成独立和自由了
It's time to take last desperate stand for individualality and freedom
Malcolm, Reese 快点
Malcolm, Reese. Get a move on
天那 Hal 你准备什么时候收拾
Oh good god Hal! When do you gonna clean this up?
Malcolm Reese 快走
Malcolm Reese, let's go!
亲爱的 我想Dewey保证要和他一起玩
Honey, I promised Dewey I'd spend time with him
一定花了大把的钱
This must have cost a fortune!
我们晚些时候再说
We'll talk about this later
我们要走了
Some of us have places to be!
Dewey 我觉得小社区需要一个学校
So Dewey, I believe our little community can use a school
我们不需要 每个人生来就聪明
We don't need it, everyone borns smart
真好儿子 是个乌托邦啊
Oh, it's beautiful son. It's Utopia
任何笨的人会被碾成食物
and anyone stupid will be ground for food
啊
Ah
吃人的乌托邦
A cannibal utopia
真有趣
Interesting
你还在这里
Oh you are still here?
我来买点东西
I was just doing some shopping and
正好到这里
I thought, while I'm was here. You know
和你打个招呼
I step over and say hi
天那 你是怎么做到的
Oh, my god. How do you that?
按压穴位
这里按的是神经
this releases the mind
这里按的是心脏
This releases the heart
你知道这是哪儿吗
And you know what this one does?
我们需要谈谈
We need to talk
我们的5个秘密会议你都没有出席
You missed our last 5 secret meetings
而且距离我们的测试不到20分钟了
and our text run is in less than 20 minutes
你为什么恨我们
Why do you hate us?
我不恨你们
Guys, I don't hate you
我只是很忙
I've just been really busy
我们还是朋友
We're still friends
- 真的吗  - 当然
- Really? - Of cause
所以你并没有退出项目
So you are not bailing on the project?
- 没有  - 那么你肯定有最终的数据
- No! - Then you have the final figures!
当然 昨天排练后算了一晚 就在我桌上
Yeah, I worked on them all night after rehearsal they're on my desk
给
Here
是其他孩子在质疑你
It was the other kids who doubt you
Malcolm 要搭车吗
Hey Malcolm. Need a ride?
我要走了
I gotta go
她分神了 我们必须现在行动
She's distracted We have to do it now!
项目启动
The program is running
让我们点火吧
Let's light this candle
准备
Ignition
点火
in
发射
Blast off
轨道看起来很诡异
It's trajectory seems rather peculiar
要知道出现错误的原因有很多
Okay, there are any number reasons  why that might have gone wrong.
它在哪儿
Where is it?
我也努力工作 但我没错过一节分娩课啊
I work hard too, but I manage to make it to Lamaze class
我们决定了
We had a vote
放弃这草吧
we want you get rid of the plant.
这小太阳花帮不上什么忙的
You can't get us all the troubles with this little sunny use
它不是阻碍 它是一种反抗
This isn't a stunt. This is an act of violence
它只是棵草
It's a plant!
你看不出吗 这不是关于植物
Can't you see. It isn't about a plant
是关于反抗专制统治和压迫的
It's about fighting tyranny fascist and oppression!
当Spangler看到这个
When Spangler sees this
他就知道他摧毁不了我们的意志 永远不会
He'll know he didn't crash our spirit and he never will
这不值得冒险
It's not worth the risk
又一次证明 看来我是这里唯一的男人
Once again it seems like I'm the only man around here
我不敢相信Nicole穿着那裙子
I can't believe Nicole wearing dress like that
可以看到她的乳头 如果她想变荡妇 可以
you can only see her nipple. If she wants to be a slut that's fine
- 但是不要让我呕心的吃不下午饭  - 我知道
- But don't make me lose my lunch - I know,
她想勾引David
she's like totally trying to impress David
但是因为David和Brenda的事 她肯定没机会
But the way he's off in Brenda's business she didn't have a chance
不敢相信我们的对话这么深入
I can't believe how deep our conversations are getting
你肯定不信我听到Josh什么了 不要告诉别人
You never gonna believe what I heard about Josh. But you can't tell anyone
我无意中在厕所
I overheard his stepsister
听到他的非亲生妹妹 他的亲生妹妹还是非亲生
When I was in the bathroom - His half sister or step sister
他的非亲生妹妹 这样他才能爱上他
No, his step sister. That's why he can  have a crush on her
- 她们在说我 对吧  - 不 我们在说Josh
- They were just talking about me weren't they? - No, we are talking about Josh
他爸爸抓到他和妹妹
Oh my god! His father like totally went down
在浴缸里后彻底抓狂了
after catching him in the hot tub with his step sister
但是我觉得他不知道整个故事
but you know what I don't even think he knows the whole story
到我了
That's my cue
我感觉抛弃天才少年享乐很罪恶
I feel guilty having so much fun and at ditching the Krelboynes
但是我肯定他们也很开心
but I'm sure they are doing fun without me
你们很幸运没人报警
You boys just lucky no one call the police
你不能证明我们火箭爆炸和
You can't prove there's any correlation between our rocket exploding
Caroline在停车场生孩子之间的关系
and Caroline giving birth at the parking lot
她和她的孩子很好 谢谢关心
She and the baby are fine. Thanks for asking
火箭
And
呢
Rocket?
天那 看来是毁了
Oh god that is true
完工了
It's finished
一个完美的社区
A perfect society
我们做了5000年来人类文明所做不到的
We have done what 5 thousand years of so called civilization couldn't do
我们创造了一个运转的世界
We create a world at works
我们
we?
你想搞破坏对吧
You wanna destroy it don't you?
是的
Yeah
我很高兴你没有
Well I appreciate that you haven't
你表现出了很强的自制力
You've shown a lot of restraint
给 尽兴
Here, Enjoy
亲爱的 我知道我们过火了 不过就此打住 我保证
Oh dear, I know we gotta a little carried away but this is it, I promise
- 没关系 我去买东西  - 你不是才去买过吗
- It's okay, I'm going grocery shopping - Did't you just go grocery shopping ?
当然 没问题
Yeah sure, no problem
- 谢谢  - Lee先生在哪里
- Thank you - Where is Mr. Lee?
- 什么  - 那个按摩师傅在哪里
- Excuse me? - The massages guy, where is he?
他不在这里工作了
Oh, he's not working here any more
什么意思 他不会不告诉我就离开的
What do you mean? That's impossible! He would never leave without telling me
我可以试着帮你问他去哪儿了
Well I can trying to find out where he move to
然后让他再次离开我
so he can leave me again
算了
Forget it!
结束了
it's over
John新打了洞
I heard John has a new piercing
给三个答案猜 不是耳朵 肚子和肚子
and I'll give you three guesses where and it's not ear or belly  belly
Julie会知道的 她趁男朋友出城和John去野营的时候
Julie would know, she went camp with one of her boyfriend with out town
John带所有女孩去野营 并说服她们裸泳
John takes all the girl camping and he's trying to  convince them to go skinny-dipping
看John不穿衣服会让我变同性恋
But I don't think John's naked will turn me up guys forever
我们应该这样
You know, we should totally do
我们应该星期六晚上开个泳池派对
We should totally have a pool party night half on Saturday
- Malcolm也来吗  - 好啊
- Malcolm want to go? - Yeah!
等等 周六我好像有事做
wait, I have something to do on Saturday
好吧 要演出
Oh yeah, the play
活着 活着
live, live
去死
Die
活着 活着 活着 活着
live, live, live live
去死
Die
由法律界元老组成的司法系统
hey, what happened to the
发生什么事了
judicial system presided over by a tribunal of wise elders
我把他们排队处死
I had 'em lined up and shot
- 儿子 你花太多时间在游戏上了 - 闭嘴 抓住他
- You know son, maybe you've been spent to much - Silence! Seize him
好吧儿子 该去睡觉了
All right son, I think it's time you goose-stepped off to bed
你在士兵面前让我丢脸了
you're embarrassing me in front of my men
Hal
Hal!
为什么这些还在这里
Why is this still here?
这不公平 为什么不带我
No fair! You did without me?!
Spangler来了 放弃那草吧
Spangler's coming lose the plant
时间到了 我们要划清界限
Time has come, we'll drawn the line
这是我们的保卫战
This is our Alamo
这个比喻不恰当 你应该明白我的意思
It's a bad example but you know what I mean
立正
Attention
这才像样
This is more like it
一切都井然有序
Everything shipshape the commanding officer enters
腰板挺直的士兵和裂缝的皮鞋
and is greeted by straightened backs
欢迎着我
And cracker of shoe leather
我知道这些天很不容易
Now I know it's been a rough couple of days
但是我们将有所提高
but we'll agree we are the better for it
我们是偏执低下的学习机器
We are a leaning meaning learning machine
你们中的人觉得我是施虐狂
Now I know that some of you think I'm a sadist
但总有一天你们会感谢我
but some day you'll thank me
兄弟 刚才太残忍了
Man, that's brutal
我们可以做些什么鼓励你
Is there anything we can do to cheer you up?
还有你妹妹的照片吗
Do you have more pictures of your sister?
我给他诅咒 他却给我爱
I give him curses, yet he gives me love
住手Hal 你越弄越糟
Hal, please stop. You're making it worse
儿子你还好吗
You okay, sport
为什么来这儿 Malcolm背叛了我们
Why are we here? Malcolm betrayed us
如果你爱一个人 就不要计较这么多
if you love something, let it go
省省你的伪哲学吧
save your cat poster philosophy for someone else
我们要
We're taking
采取极端方法
the highroad
你们只是相互欺骗
But you were totally scamming together
不 我们只是暧昧
No. We were just smacking
她说她只是和Andrew在派对上玩玩
She claims she was just "hanging out" with Andrew at the party
但是他们真的搞在一起
but they were really hooking up.
我不敢相信她竟然
I can not believe she would
够了 握住或者丢弃
Enough. Hold, or cut both strings
到我了吗 快把我放下去
Was that my cue? Quick, lower me.
这应该就是那些只有几秒钟
This must be one of those times when it feels like an eternity
却像一辈子的时候
but only a few seconds have gone by.
为啥Malcolm五分钟没有说话了
How com Malcolm didn't say anything in 5 minutes?
台词呢
Line
我会很享受这种情况 但这太惨了
Normally I would enjoy something like that but this is just sad
喂 精灵 你飘流到哪里去
How now, spirit? Wither wander you?
国王今晚让他在这里的狂欢
The King doth keep his revels here tonight.
所以 大家晚安 如果我们是朋友 给我你的手
So, good night unto you all.Give me your hands if we be friends
罗宾会去赎罪的
and Robin shall restore amends.
结束了 你答应我有裸露场景的
It's over? You promised a partial nudity
骗你的啦
Yeah that was a lie
之后的冰激凌呢
And ice cream after?
也是骗你的
that too
喂 精灵 你飘流到哪里去
How now, spirit? Wither wander you?
国王今晚让他在这里的狂欢
The King doth keep his revels here tonight.
我就知道我记得
I knew I knew it!